markaboo.com 2008-03-08

# MarkaBoo :: better bookmarks for everyone

## TGLO PRIVACY POLICY

theglobe.com, Inc. and its subsidiary tglo Holdings, Inc. ("Company") will not trade, sell, or disclose to any third party any form of subscriber identifiable information without the consent of the subscriber (except as required by subpoena, search warrant or other legal process or in the case where failure to disclose information will lead to imminent harm to the subscriber or others). This includes information derived from registration, subscription, and use of the Company's service. As a publicly traded company, the Company is required to file numerous reports with different administrative bodies. As such, the Company may provide aggregate statistics about subscribers, sales and traffic patterns. None of these reports or statistics will include personally identifiable information.

Collection / Use of Information The Company will collect and use subscriber identifiable information for billing, provisioning of service, resolution of problems associated with service, 411 type directory services, and to inform subscribers of new products or services that will enhance the Company's ability to provide service to subscribers. The Company will use subscriber identifiable information to market products and services to the subscriber, but will not disclose or make available any subscriber identifiable information to any third parties seeking to market products. If a subscriber chooses in writing not to participate in direct marketing of new products and services from the Company then subscriber's information will not be used for the purpose of marketing new products. Additionally, the subscriber may request to have identifiable information deleted from the Company's directory.

Security The Company has invested and deployed a wide variety of technology and security features to ensure the privacy of subscriber information on its network. In addition, the Company has implemented strict operations guidelines to ensure subscriber privacy is safeguarded. The Company will continue to revise policies and implement additional security features as new technologies becomes available. However, Company cannot guarantee in any way that information provided to Company by subscriber may not be illegally obtained from Company.

Communications The Company will not read, listen to or disclose to any third parties private e-mail, conversations, or other communications that are transmitted using the Company services, except as required to ensure proper operation of services or as otherwise authorized by law.

Unlawful Activity The Company may use subscriber identifiable information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of service, the network integrity, that otherwise violate the Company's Service Agreements or activities that are or may be illegal.

Account Information The subscriber is responsible for ensuring that the information on file with the Company is current and accurate.

Children's Privacy Policy We have developed this site to appeal only to visitors eighteen and older. However visitors of all ages may navigate through our website. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of thirteen. If upon notification by a parent, or discovery by other means, that a child under thirteen has improperly registered on the site by using false information, we will immediately cancel the child's membership and participation, and delete all personally identifiable information, user name and password from our records (personal information). If you believe that a minor has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at feedback@markaboo.com

### DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACT

Digital Millennium Copyright Act It is our policy to respond to notices of alleged infringement that comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the text of which can be found at the U.S. Copyright Office Web Site, http://lcWeb.loc.gov/copyright/) and other applicable intellectual property laws, which may include removing or disabling access to material claimed to be the subject of infringing activity. If we remove or disable access to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, we will make a good-faith attempt to contact the owner or administrator of each affected site so that they may make a counter notification pursuant to sections 512(g)(2) and (3) of that Act. It is our policy to document all notices of alleged infringement on which we act.

Infringement Notification To file a notice of infringement with us, you must provide a written communication (by fax or regular mail -- not by e-mail, except by prior agreement) that sets forth the items specified below. Please note that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) if you materially misrepresent that a product or activity is infringing your copyrights. Accordingly, if you are not sure whether certain material of yours is protected by copyright laws, we suggest that you first contact an attorney.

To expedite our ability to process your request, please use the following format (including section numbers): 1\. Identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work that you believe has been infringed. For example, "The copyrighted work at issue is the text that appears on www.markaboo.com/people/example/."

2\. Identify the material that you claim is infringing the copyrighted work listed in item #1 above.

3\. Provide information reasonably sufficient to permit theglobe.com or any of its subsidiaries to contact you (e-mail address is preferred).

4\. Provide information, if possible, sufficient to permit theglobe.com or any of its subsidiaries to notify the owner/administrator of the web page that allegedly contains infringing material (e-mail address is preferred).

5\. Include the following statement: "I have a good faith belief that use of the copyrighted materials described above on the allegedly infringing web pages is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law."

6\. Include the following statement: "I swear, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate and that I am the copyright owner or am authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed."

7\. Sign the paper.

8\. Send the written communication to the following address:

theglobe.com  
Trademark Infringement Complaints  
110 E. Broward Boulevard  
14th Floor  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301  
ATTN: Edward Cespedes  

Counter Notification The administrator of an affected site may make a counter notification pursuant to sections 512(g)(2) and (3) of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. When we receive a counter notification, we will reinstate the material in question.

To file a counter notification with us, you must provide a written communication (by fax or regular mail -- not by e-mail, except by prior agreement) that sets forth the items specified below. Please note that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) if you materially misrepresent that a product or activity is not infringing the copyrights of others. Accordingly, if you are not sure whether certain material infringes the copyrights of others, we suggest that you first contact an attorney.

To expedite our ability to process your counter notification, please use the following format (including section numbers):

1\. Identify the specific URLs of material that theglobe.com has removed or to which theglobe.com has disabled access.

2\. Provide your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the judicial district in which your address is located (or Fort Lauderdale, Florida if your address is outside of the United States), and that you will accept service of process from the person who provided notification under subsection (c)(1)(C) or an agent of such person.

3\. Include the following statement: "I swear, under penalty of perjury, that I have a good faith belief that each search result or message identified above was removed or disabled as a result of a mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled."

4\. Sign the paper.

5\. Send the written communication to the following address:

theglobe.com  
Trademark Infringement Complaints  
110 E. Broward Boulevard  
14th Floor  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301  
ATTN: Edward Cespedes
